{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "If you were buying coffee grounds for a turkish press, what would you buy?",
      "options": [
        "Very finely ground coffee",
        "Coffee ground for a basket filter",
        "Very coarsely ground coffee",
        "Coffee for an espresso machine"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Coffee plants originated on what continent over 1000 years ago?",
      "options": [
        "Africa",
        "Europe",
        "South America",
        "Asia"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How many pounds of coffee beans will one coffee plant produce in a year?",
      "options": [
        "1-2 pounds",
        "5 pounds",
        "6 pounds",
        "8 pounds"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Coffee cultivation began in which century?",
      "options": [
        "The twentieth century",
        "The eighteenth century",
        "The tenth century, bc",
        "The fifteenth century"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What country is the world's largest producer of coffee, producing 35% of all coffee consumed?",
      "options": [
        "Guatemala",
        "Colombia",
        "Brazil",
        "The United States"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the fruit of the coffee plant called?",
      "options": [
        "The coffee cherry",
        "The seed",
        "The fruit",
        "The coffee bean"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What percentage of the contents of a cup of black coffee is water?",
      "options": [
        "90%",
        "98%",
        "95%",
        "75%"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of plant does the coffee bean come from?",
      "options": [
        "A perennial",
        "An annual",
        "An evergreen tree",
        "A shrub"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "\nin what year was the first coffee tree grown in the first european greenhouse?",
      "options": [
        "1875",
        "1492",
        "1715",
        "1812"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Where does arabica coffee originate?",
      "options": [
        "Qatar",
        "Ethiopia",
        "Italy",
        "Arabia"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who brought coffee cultivation to their colonies in java and sumatra?",
      "options": [
        "The Portuguese",
        "The British",
        "The Dutch",
        "The French"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    }
  ]
}